http://aaoklahoma.org/legal-stuff/privacy-policy

AA Oklahoma – Privacy Policy
Area 57 A.A. Web site This information is provided to explain our online information practices and the choices you have in the way information is collected and used on this Web site.
The Information We Collect
At the AAOklahoma Web site, we do not require personally identifiable information from you in order to access and use the Web site. Certain functions, such as new group registration forms or updates, do require you to voluntarily submit personally identifiable information, which may include: name, address, email, and telephone numbers.
How We Use the Information
Any personally identifiable information submitted by you is kept strictly confidential and separately from the Web site, and is used solely by Area 57 to provide the information to AAWS, the Oklahoma City Intergroup, or NE Central Services that you submitted for your group registration or update. We do not provide or forward personally identifiable information to any organization.
Cookies
We do not set cookies on your machine. Most browsers and certain third-party utilities allow for you to accept or deny cookies from this or any other Web site.
Third Party Sites
Portions of Area 57’s Web site contain links to other Web sites. When leaving our Web site you should consult the other Web site’s privacy statement for more information, as those practices may differ from ours.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy statement, you may contact us at:
Alcoholics Anonymous
Oklahoma State Committee Area 57 Office
4509 N. Classen Blvd.
